Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/linhnguyen-977a81129 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Customer Service

Management

Microsoft PowerPoint

Languages

English (Professional Working)

Linh Nguyen

Software Tester at FPT Software

Vietnam

Summary

I am very careful, honest and high-responsibility. In addition, I am also agile and adapt quickly to the new environment.

In short-term, I want to improve my knowledge and experience in Testing and become an excellent employee.

In long-term, I wish became a Senior Tester, make the contribution to the development of company.

Experience

FPT Software Software Tester April 2016 - Present (9 years)

32 Floor, Keangnam Landmark Building, Pham Hung, Tu Liem, Ha Noi

- Study software requirement specification
- Create test cases
- Set up test environment, prepare test data
- Execute test and report results to Team Leader
- Logged defects during the test execution phase
- Support, training for new member in Testing.
- Good knowledge of software development process, test process, tracking bugs, test technique
- Knowledge and experience of testing techniques
- Became a key member of the project

Viettel ICT

Tester Intern

April 2015 - August 2015 (5 months)

C'Land Building, Le Duc Tho, Tu Liem, Ha Noi

- Analyze customer requirement
- Create test cases and execute testing
- Logged defects on Mantis tool
- Create report to Manager
- Have knowledge basis on SQL Server, Oracle

Bkav Corp.

Customer Service Collaborator

April 2014 - March 2015 (1 year)

HH1 Building, Duong Dinh Nghe, Trung Hoa, Cau Giay, Ha Noi

- Call customer in order to invite to buy Bkav Pro
- Receive, process information, comment and answer customer requirements over telephone
- Persuaded customer to use Bkav Pro
- Achieved some silver prizes, bronze prizes in many weeks

Education

Vietnam University of Commerce

· (2011 - 2015)